Welcome to my world.
Won't you hold it?
Miracles I guess.
Still happen now and then.
Yeah.
Oh.
Ooh.
For most of human civilization, we believed
that we were Earth's most dominant species.
We believe that life could only
exist on the surface of the planet.
Well, after a certain
point, you have to wonder.
What else were we wrong about?
We have maps less than 5% of all the worth.
But our ecosystems are linked in
ways we never could have imagined.
We are not two separate worlds.
We're one.
Kong is settling in to how worth.
So the big guy likes his new home.
We think so?
His species was a very social one.
It's not natural for Kong to be so alone.
He's the last of his kind.
Every day, he searches for
a family that he'll never find.
What about Godzilla?
Godzilla's on the surface?
Kong is below.
As long as they don't
venture into each other's
territories, we've got
nothing to worry about.
Humanity is lucky.
Godzilla's fighting the battles we can't.
Kong setting in for the night
looks like it was another rough one.
That's the part that's gone yet.
Maybe he was looking forward to date.
Good luck with that.
I hope he's up for some
meters, please see the romance.
Whoa.
Simple, detected in sector five.
That's cons hunting ground.
More electrical anomalies?
I don't think so, man.
I haven't seen anything like this before.
I always should tell
the right to have them.
I'll type it up.
There's whole places in that anomaly.
It's so near.
Tell the Italian military, Rome would
be flattened if it weren't for Godzilla.
They couldn't threaten him all they want.
Just tell them to find another scapegoat.
Director Hampton, what's up?
Well, out close one is seven, aren't you?
And they see this over.
You might want to take a look.
Is this from the sensor array?
Yeah, we've been getting
some pretty weird spikes.
I mean, it could just
be regular interference.
Yeah, but it keeps happening.
Mm-hmm.
We should prep a
server to interesting case.
Okay.
And what about Godzilla?
Oh, he's just sleeping.
Like a big angry baby.
Let's hope it stays that way.
He's like so late.
Everyone, eyes from
your own paper, all right?
Let's make sure we circle the answers.
Really?
Your daughter is intelligent,
but she's not engaged.
Her grades are slipping.
She's not interacting
with any of her friends.
And these problems aren't
going away, Dr. Andrews.
They've been getting worse.
OK, I'm sorry.
She's just still adjusting to our world.
I understand that, but we have a number
of students who are culturally displaced.
Sure, but her culture is not displaced.
She is her culture.
She's the last living member of the E.V.
tribe.
We're just trying to reach her.
I know.
Join the club.
And I believe you.
For centuries, the E.W.
tribe were the guardians of Star Island,
the ancestral home of the Great Kong.
But when shifting storm patterns
destroyed the island, the E.W.
were annihilated.
With only a single member
of the tribe having survived,
a young girl found and rescued
amid the punishing storm.
Her fellow villagers were
lost with a touch, gone
to history, just like the
Great Kongsans had said.
Nothing wrong with you.
You perfect.
So will you be with the next Titan attacks?
How will you protect the things
and people that matter most to you?
Today's podcast is brought to you by Gargantuan Shurance,
the only insurance company that provides tight protection
for your home and personal belongings, because Godzilla may
not care about your hopes and dreams, but Gargantuan does.
Oh, okay, Titan Chasers!
Oh, we have got anybody
who will touch on today's show.
We're recording in progress, go away!
Yes, I just want to let everyone
know that there is no place for flex.
I'm going unbelievable.
What?
Hi, Bernie.
Eileen Andrews, we met in Hong Kong.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hong Kong.
Yeah, that was so long ago.
Go.
Go
I was wondering if I could
get your help with something.
Me.
Uh, sure.
Sure.
Yeah?
Of course.
Come on in.
Dr. Andrews.
OK. Yeah?
Just straight down
there all there to the left.
Have a seat.
What can I help you with, you
know, me, Casa, A, Sue, home?
OK, so the sequence on
the right, this is a signal
that's been interfering with
our equipment and hallowars.
OK. And these are drawings
by my daughter, Gia, and
you're going to think
that I'm completely insane.
Well, the patterns are the
same in the middle section.
Exactly.
Thank you.
Look, our analysts, they
don't know what to make of this.
They're talking in circles.
They're saying radio
interference, coincidence.
But I know that you
think outside of the box.
I didn't know who else to turn to.
And they sent you here because...
No, don't send me.
I came here.
You know, that's what's ironic.
You know, Monarch wouldn't
confirm my crucial part in
taking down Mechagotzilla,
which cost me thousands of...
hundreds of subscribers on my blog.
Oh, and the troll who saw
the trolls online, they question
every single thing that I put
up, especially this one troll.
This one troll named the door stands 64.
You ever heard of them?
No, I don't think so.
Great, because he's a trash bag, OK?
I'm more qualified than half of those
people that you have working over there.
I knew what Godzilla was going to
do before anybody would want to say.
This is why I am here, Bernie.
I am here, OK?
Can you help me or not?
It depends.
Are you the new boss down at the mess?
The Monarch Hollow Earth
Station, the MHS, the mess.
Yeah, nobody calls it that.
I run the Kong Research
Division, but technically,
Director Hampton is in
charge of general operations.
Well, Director Hampton doesn't
have a kid who can talk to Kong.
You want to go to Hollow Earth?
I'm so glad I didn't have to say it.
I thought you were never going to ask.
But I really give me proof.
And that would help me
with my bonafides for my blog.
And I knew that you would be
the person that helped me do that.
OK. Well, if this happens and
that is a big ifs, then Monarch
would need, you know, whatever
you guys call it, Final Cut on it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, who
You work out what's going on, and I
will get you anything that you want, OK?
That is a promise.
Well, anything is alive, but that's
very, that's very generous for that.
And we have to go right now.
What?
Godzilla is on the move again.
I'm going to go.
Okay, listen to me.
If Godzilla's on the move,
he senses a threat coming.
We don't know what it is.
Of course we're concerned, Senator.
That's why we're monitoring the situation.
What is it?
And I am telling you, Senator,
that Kong doesn't leave
Hollywood, which is why
Godzilla has no reason to tell you.
That's what you're doing up here.
No idea.
Just got Zil enough.
Not that we can tell.
It was only a matter of time.
And what happens if
Godzilla starts hitting this way?
And we all run like hell.
Right, the good news is
it's just an infected tooth.
But luckily you've come
to the best Jotrin town.
percent, vital stable.
Trapper, you are clear to swarm
the damage to a quick replacement.
Hey!
Touchdown, Trapper.
Do you have the breakfast?
Yeah, this sucker's ready to come out.
There she is.
Trapper.
Thanks for getting down here so fast.
Nice work.
You are most welcome.
It's not every day.
You get to climb inside
a 300 foot eight mouth.
Is it?
Yeah.
I'm sure it's going to be strong enough.
The tooth?
Yeah.
That's the same polymer composite
that you use on the vehicle heat shield.
You chomp through
the rifle tower, actually.
Well, good tooth aren't going to help
if Godzilla senses the haze up here.
Well, you can't have a
tighten with a tooth eight can it?
No.
Don't worry.
A couple of hours.
You might be a bit groggy,
but it'll be good to go back down.
You know, I first heard that
you were going to be a vet.
I thought, no, that is way
too boring for Trapper.
Then you go and become
the weirdest vet in the world.
Yeah, it's basically me and
Dr. Doolittle set my animals a bigger.
I thought, finally, someone
has made him grow up.
Nope.
Someone tried that back in
college, but didn't really work.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, well, she said to me,
Trapper, you are not a serious person.
Oh, she sounds very smart.
Yeah.
Yeah, she's got a PhD.
Two, actually.
That's a kid day.
You know, struggling, trying
to find a replacement a world.
Yeah, I know where that goes.
Now, Ari, she'll be all right.
She's got a good mum.
Dr. Andrews, your guest
has been asking for you.
Please don't take this the
wrong way, but can I just say,
there's a research library
has many glaring omissions.
I had to call in some serious
favors from my Discord chat.
Bernie, do you have something?
Yes, I've got something.
I do have something.
Whatever signal you guys are picking up.
OK, we have seen similar
patterns with PD over time.
And each spike corresponds
with a specific Titan event.
Can you hold this, please?
Thank you so much.
OK, check this out.
See this?
King Diora.
First encounter with Godzilla.
Here.
Discovery of Skull Island.
All right, so what you're saying is that
these signals aren't just random patterns.
Yeah, it seems that way, yes.
And Godzilla's picking up on it.
Oh, I can do you one better now.
Look, I've looked at
points of similarities in
each waveform, and I
compare them to that pattern.
Everybody is in the stress call.
It's a distress call.
A psychic energy SLM skill.
If your daughter is
seeing these symbols,
then something down
there is calling for help.
Regular sound waves, they can't
propagate this far without decay.
This, this is something that we have never
encountered, and it's getting stronger.
You got a working theory?
You're going to tell the
perfect alien language.
Some sort of distress signal.
Signal?
From what?
Or from who?
Well, whatever is.
This is what Godzilla's on the move.
We can't say for sure,
but it seems that way.
Well, we have to figure this out fast.
The wolves are already at our door.
The government has
been looking for an excuse
to take over Hall of
War with operations.
And the corporations are looking at chops.
Yeah, because who wants to be
rich and get rid of all the monsters?
May not be terrible, right?
We'd better find the source
before DC gets wind of this.
OK.
I'm giving you full operational oversight.
Take a small team.
We can't make it fast
and don't leave anyone die.
We'll be in the car before night for you.
You feel like I'm for a ride?
So you never ask.
Waking Waking everyone.
Calms out.
Come on, we have a deal.
Bernie, this isn't sightseeing
at the reconnaissance mission.
Well, so I see how it is.
When you need something, it's all, you're
so smart, Bernie, you're so capable, Bernie,
I'll subscribe to your Titan blog, Bernie,
and then when I deliver it, you toss me aside.
Okay, look, this could be dangerous.
Come on.
I have no stranger to danger.
I didn't mean to rhyme that time.
Look, you owe me.
OK, I help crack this thing.
This could be like last time
when we saved the world.
Remember?
Mm-hmm.
Miguel?
Yeah.
Privacy for one more.
Thank you, Dr. Andrew.
You will not regret it.
You're kidding, right?
I'm the plus one.
Hello.
We are going to Hallo Earth.
I am going to Hallo Earth.
Oh, my God, what am I doing?
So is there, like, an inflate briefing
that I should know about, you know?
Yeah, there is.
There's no parachutes,
no flotation devices.
You touch into this
stuff, you lose your hand,
and if you die, make
sure it's outside my vehicle.
Good briefing.
Great briefing.
Don't take me care too personally.
Aggression is his love language.
All right, Miguel.
Let's do this.
No, not to swallow your tongue.
What?
Turn up and swallow my tongue.
I don't know what that means.
Darn it!
It's over!
Rock systems active.
Systems team lost.
All systems good, Doc.
How's everyone there?
You alright?
Never better.
Yeah.
Burning, you good?
Nice, huh?
Oh, wow.
Looks like Con is headed home.
How far are they outposts?
100 clicks.
Still not answering Con's.
Passivity alert.
Predators nine o'clock.
Where?
Who?
Those are vertices, Micko.
They're called vertices.
Some of they're from?
No, they're totally harmless.
Unless you're getting
rolled up and then they
think about a lightning
bolt with a bioelectricity.
predators know to stay well away,
which makes them the perfect chaperone
if you happen to have a tall, biomimic
quick hammer blast, which we do.
Talk to me.
It's not good.
Godzilla just made landfall in France.
Ground team is five clicks out.
We got picture.
Oh my god, it's a nuclear facility.
The atmosphere of
radiation levels are dropping.
He's absorbing it.
Okay, he's charging for something.
We're coming up on out post one.
Oh God.
You've seen the stock.
Yeah, yeah, I'm saying it.
Well, there's no heat signatures.
It's so much for survivors.
God, I have some respect.
These people had families.
Where could have done this?
I don't understand.
We've had this outpost
for years without incident.
So why attack now?
What changed?
Here, Doc.
There's a camera here.
You reckon you can pull
any footage off of that?
Oh, shit.
Oh, that's not common.
That's something else.
Yeah.
Let's get off the ground before
that something else comes back.
Cool.
Mm.
Hmm.
Thank you.
I'm getting anything on first thing.
Yeah, I'm just... Oh, my God.
Here.
Take a look.
It looks like an ape,
but that's impossible.
What the bloody hell is that?
I have no idea.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
The hell was that, Michael?
I'm done.
I must have been the signal.
The same electrical disturbances
for happening at the outpost.
System stabilized.
Oh, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, shit.
Who says it's coming from that rich point?
Well, let's take a look.
OK, it's close again.
The hollow earth.
The world untouched by mankind.
Is this how Neil Armstrong felt
when he stepped on alien soil?
Is this one small step for
me and one giant leap?
Are you kidding me?
Write down the lens.
It's a documentary.
You want to be natural, just walk.
Take two.
Be hollow earth, a world.
All right, guys.
That bridge, you pointed out,
it's about two miles straight ahead.
I'm getting it alive out here.
Oh, look at that.
That must be tasty to me.
Keller.
Only female musky toes drink the
land, so that you grow their eggs.
She needs a call on me.
Wait.
What?
What's the holdup?
Not this way.
What?
Why?
Now we've got to take a
detour to something here.
Where?
Where here?
Back here?
Here?
No, I'm not picking anything up.
No, something doesn't smell right.
It's not just you, Miguel.
You smell that?
It's like a rotting flesh.
It's probably just a carcass of wind.
Can we keep moving?
Miguel, hold up.
Listen, pal.
I'm going to trust my
steady out thermal over your
ace finchura hippie-dippy
six cents all day long.
There's no need to call
people name for you free show.
If you don't shut it, I'm
gonna take that camera.
I'm gonna shove it right up your ass.
I'm a charge.
We move.
What if we just listen to somebody call me?
I said I'm a charge.
We should be all right.
Those things don't reach that far.
He was just eating by a tree.
What you doing, Doc?
I'm trying to call the base for expansion.
Women, he was there ready.
He was waiting my face and
then a tree out of nowhere.
I know, man.
I know.
That's heavy.
But that's a natural world, man.
Red, intuitive and cool.
Tennyson, you just watched a
man get devoured by a topiary
nightmare, and you want to
quote Tennyson down here.
Yeah, man.
Ain't you all about it?
Let love class grief, man.
Come here.
Yeah, humans, we think we took
ourselves off the food chamber.
Maybe.
Maybe the titans are here to remind us.
I think that there is something
seriously wrong with you.
OK, OK, OK.
It's not working.
We better move on.
We'll mourn later.
Yeah, come on.
Come on, buddy.
Let's do it.
It was even by a tree.
I don't want to die like that.
Not by a tree.
No, we can't get any closer than this.
Godzilla's burning hole with radiation.
Whatever he's headed
for hasn't really pissed off.
This morning, 15 Alpha over.
15 Alpha responding.
Godzilla's current trajectory is showing
him heading towards the Arctic Ocean.
What titans are in the area?
Looks like he's hunting team, right?
classified file 3-2-4.
Titan is Tiamat.
Titan 19.
Extremely aggressive, territorial.
Weaponizing her body of razor sharp scales,
Tiamat's Arctic layer sits in the direct path of
electromagnetically charged solar winds, making
it the largest stockpile of energy on Earth.
If Godzilla takes down
Tiamat, he'll supercharge.
This ruins human civilization.
Down here.
The markings are older than the
ones on skull and centuries older.
But the architecture is
consistent with the eerie
Oh, this is wonderful.
Yeah, that's what he is.
There's no moss on these ones.
No.
Mothra, Queen of the
Monsters, and Hollow Earth.
Her lineage must go back
further than we thought.
No, no, no.
Hey!
It's like some kind of
an irrigation system.
I mean, this predates everything.
Let's contain me as the Lemurias of these.
He's got one of the first, man.
It's just who's going.
I don't know.
It's a trip.
Great model.
Let's call you.
Look at that.
What kind of creative is this?
Agent Alien astronauts.
Who is he?
The water's running underneath.
And this is all canning.
Here.
I'm going to buy our electric hum.
It's like a camouflage.
This must be the source of the signal.
We've got to check this out.
Oh.
I'm ready.
you
Thank you very much.
Oh.
Take it forward.
Salut running.
Five knots.
He's gone to do much later.
Wait, what did she say?
She says we're not alone.
See, I knew I knew I felt something.
Come on then.
Oh, my God.
He's in the tire.
He was civilization
protected within all the world.
These structures, they
look like they've been
carved from some
enormous quartz crystal.
That must be their energy source.
I'm feeling the energy, but let's
just keep it together, all right?
He should make eye contact with him.
It's considered polite.
Yeah, this is this is not working for me.
Oh.
No, I think I'm gonna catch him.
Tell the path to Clay.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't take her off.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Hey!
Don't put it!
you
Let's go, let's go.
The beacon that we've been
following, it's the eerie kind for help.
So what they send out is SOS.
And then what?
Godzilla hears it?
They work him up.
And as always, for a while, they already
live in a nightmare monster hellscape.
What could possibly scare them?
She understands me.
And a nightmare monster hellscape
is a wonderful place to raise a family.
This whole room is covered in eerie script.
It says that in the beginning, Hollow Earth
lived in harmony with the surface world.
The titans were the
guardians of nature, and the
great apes became the
protectors of humanity.
but a great evil threatened the peace.
A powerful and ruthless ape desperate
to conquer the surface world led
his tribe into war against the one
they call the monster who ate a star.
There's more.
The war with the apes
nearly destroyed Godzilla.
But after a great battle, he imprisoned the
apes in a fiery realm with Hall of Wirth.
Their false king remains
obsessed with reaching the surface.
The ewe call him the scar king.
Oh.
Mm.
He controlled her with pain.
Her power covered the
earth in the last Ice Age.
We brought Kong down here.
He's been looking for others
like himself, going deeper
into Hollowworth and
getting closer to their prison.
The Ewe must have known it was
just a matter of time, and that's why
they've been calling for help,
and that's why Godzilla's changing.
He's carrying up the Wild Wolf story.
He barely survived last time.
What's Godzilla gonna do on his own?
He won't be on his own.
The Iwi believe that at the end of
the world, one of their own will return.
And awaken Mothra, defender of
the Iwi and ancient ally of Godzilla.
They believe that their Savior
will be an Iwi from Scotland.
It seems like a lot to pour on one kid.
Come on.
This is when our air team debays,
tracking up for Godzilla's location.
We've closed the shipping
lanes within 300 miles.
Plasma readings indicate he's
absorbing everything in there.
You know, I made a deal with
myself when I became a mother.
I said to myself, I don't care what you
have to sacrifice, what you have to give up.
You will do right by that little girl.
I just never thought that the
thing I'd be giving up would be her.
Look, you don't know that.
Really?
Trapper, before we came here, she
said that she didn't belong anywhere.
This is the life that she wants,
and I have to give her up.
I have no funny term.
Does everything feel lighter, Delis?
Yeah, do this.
I have a little bit,
a little bit, a little bit.
The whole story, too.
That must weigh a ton.
Yeah.
Yes, see, I don't know how they can do
it, but somehow they're able to move the
pyramid's positions, which disrupts
the gravitational pull down here in this.
That's how they run their city.
An entire civilization built
off the manipulation of gravity.
God, I wish I was streaming this large.
What are you going to do with that, Bern?
Look, I know what you're thinking,
but you don't understand, OK?
To bend through what
I've been through, sing what
I've seen, and have
absolutely nobody believe you.
This place, this place is special, man.
This magic.
How long do you think it'll stay like that?
It's not posting that about.
Like you look at any isolated
tribe or community, how
many of them survive
contact with the outside world?
You know, I think you're pretty in vain.
You already saved the world once.
Can't say that away from you.
Could you say that all again?
The last part?
That's what I happen on footage.
What?
Oh, what we have to find
out what that was, right?
He's got a mini comb.
How did they find this place?
He must have sensed you.
That arm looks bad.
That's worse than bad.
That's frostbite.
I better go take a look.
you
Protecting onto the energy signature.
Oh my god.
It's changed Nobody likes a
dentist Let's get a look at that.
Oh big guy
Trapper, he looks really hard.
Yeah, it's not great.
I'm seeing nerve damage.
It's a significant tissue loss.
So what are we saying?
He's not going to last a day
down here with only one arm.
Yeah, communication
to the surface is still out.
If I can get back to
the outpost, I think
there might be some
supplies that we can use.
I don't think a massive cast
is going to solve the problem.
I wasn't talking plaster of Paris.
I'm thinking more along the
line to project powerhouse.
You can't be serious.
Oh, I'm deadly serious.
That prototype was almost
finished when they pulled the funding.
All right, well, what
are you still doing here?
I love you too, Doc.
Project Powerhouse, what is that?
Exactly.
After Mecha Godzilla,
we realized that there
were some threats that
even calm couldn't face.
So we started working on
some minor augmentations.
Oh.
with what kind of augmentations.
Making one of the
strongest titans even stronger
didn't go over so well,
so we got shut down.
Lucky for us, the prototype had already
been transported to Hollywood for testing.
It's stored in the armory at Outpost 1.
What do you think of that?
That's one hell of an
augmentation there, Trapper.
Only the best for Mr. Kong.
All right, ready to go.
All right, there he goes.
He's moving.
We got this.
There's a bit rough from
ready, but he should hold.
It's good.
Looks good, Trapper.
Damn good.
See if they can love it, or he's
going to rip it off with his teeth.
Ah!
I think he loves it!
The scarring.
Hey, hey, why are you telling me?
Where's he going?
Godzilla won't come down
here unless Kong brings him.
Okay, the last time those two
met up was almost the end of Kong.
He's taking a hell of a race.
If I'm your ladies to start a war.
Yeah, that's a sort of sad mission.
We have con draws Godzilla down here.
They can make their stand in Hall
of Wirth and then there's a chance
that Godzilla can stop scarking
and Shimo from reaching the surface.
We are absolutely certain
that she can pull this off, right?
It's why Jia was called here.
Only an eerie from Skull Island.
Gonna wake in Mothra.
And Mothra is the key
to Godzilla protecting
this place, and it's
pathways to the surface.
She's gonna be her, huh?
Yeah.
Hey, she's evacuated in the villages.
Gravity, gravity, the
pyramids and gravity, I got it.
I got it now.
Tell me on the way.
Come on, come on.
Well, we are throwing
random shit at the wall.
Permission to take the heat.
Rally some reinforcements.
To the surface?
No, there's no time.
No, this idea is way way better than that.
No!
Yeah!
Oh.
All right, we're underneath the pyramids.
Now one.
Gravity.
Ewe technology.
with the chemical reaction this liquid metal becomes an engineering mechanism
forcing the two electromagnetic pyramids together causing an anti-gravity
shockwave but only for a few minutes or maybe less which should keep those
things from the portals after that everything that is up will come crashing down
in here.
We're not going to make
it this time enough time.
We need something to slow them down.
What else can we do?
He's supposed to see mating season.
You're carried away.
I'm gonna just do on the mountain.
Backing up your beautiful paper.
Open your way up.
No, the young team's out.
They've already served us.
Let's take it out of them.
How much do you think?
Yes!
Sit and protect in the portal!
Whoa!
No!
It's so good.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
I'm so proud of you.
Look, I...
I know that this place, you, like home,
And I want you to know that
whenever you decide, I suppose.
What am I talking?
I assume you want to stay.
This place could be your home.
You're right.
Thank you, thank you, thank you
for the world in the time of our day.
you
.
Oh.
you.
.
I'm sorry.